<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on C. Silva</title>
        <link>https://cfsilva.com/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on C. Silva</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://cfsilva.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Motivation is the Power of Life Systems.</title>
            <link>https://cfsilva.com/posts/motivation_from_life_systems/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://cfsilva.com/posts/motivation_from_life_systems/</guid>
            <description>In the common understanding, motivation often appears elusive, striking us randomly or evading us altogether. Some believe it&amp;rsquo;s discipline, not motivation, that propels us forward.
I propose it&amp;rsquo;s a harmonious blend of both.
Here&amp;rsquo;s how 10 Push-Ups a Day can transform your life: Motivation is not just a mental state; it&amp;rsquo;s woven into our life systems. It thrives as we cultivate daily habits, no matter how small, which accumulate momentum and transform our lives, like a snowball.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In the common understanding, motivation often appears elusive, striking us randomly or evading us altogether. Some believe it&rsquo;s discipline, not motivation, that propels us forward.</p>
<p>I propose it&rsquo;s a harmonious <strong>blend of both</strong>.</p>
<h3 id="heres-how-10-push-ups-a-day-can-transform-your-life">Here&rsquo;s how 10 Push-Ups a Day can transform your life:</h3>
<p>Motivation is not just a mental state; it&rsquo;s woven into our life systems. It thrives as we cultivate daily habits, no matter how small, which accumulate momentum and transform our lives, like a snowball.</p>
<p>Here&rsquo;s a quick example:</p>
<p>You get up at 6am, it&rsquo;s a Monday. You immediately drink water and do 10 Push Ups. You feel great and this now motivates you to make your bed. You feel productive and that you started the day on the right foot, making your bed now motivates you to cook an healthy breakfast. Cooking a good breakfast makes you feel healthy and ready to take on the day. You crush it at work, now you&rsquo;re even motivated to go to the gym!</p>
<p>You get home, you feel amazing and productive, you feel motivated to take care of yourself, create a little self-help routine and even cook an healthy dinner! You go to bed, you had an amazing day and you feel incredible.</p>
<p>Amazing days lead to amazing weeks that eventually lead to amazing years and a good life.</p>
<p>This is how, <strong>small habits transform your life</strong>.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
