<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on C. Silva</title>
    <link>https://cfsilva.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on C. Silva</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cfsilva.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Circadian</title>
      <link>https://cfsilva.com/projects/circadian/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cfsilva.com/projects/circadian/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Circadian is a lightweight and self-hostable Fitness Tracker using Docker. The users will be able to daily log their weight/bodyfat, upload a daily picture and also log their workouts.&#xA;There&amp;rsquo;s also a statistics tab where can users will be able to see their progress in charts and click on each daily log to see the details&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s currently in development.&#xA;Tech Stack Being built using SvelteKit + Prisma + SQLite, DaisyUI for easy styling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GamingFacts-API</title>
      <link>https://cfsilva.com/projects/gamingfacts-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cfsilva.com/projects/gamingfacts-api/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A simple api that returns a random interesting fact about videogames/gaming.&#xA;I wholeheartedly believe in learning-by-doing, so this is my first step into learning Go.&#xA;How it works It&amp;rsquo;s a simple GET request. You can test it out using:&#xA;curl https://gamingfacts.cfsilva.com/ The response should look like this:&#xA;{ &amp;#34;fact&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;The first game to use a game engine was &amp;#39;Space Rogue&amp;#39; in 1989.&amp;#34; } Tech Stack The project was built using Go</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huex</title>
      <link>https://cfsilva.com/projects/huex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cfsilva.com/projects/huex/</guid>
      <description>What is Huex? Huex is a command line based tool to control the devices you have configured in your Conbee II.&#xA;This tool utilizes the Conbee II REST API.&#xA;Tech Stack The project was built using Python&#xA;Github Repo You can find the project repo here</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motivation is the Power of Life Systems.</title>
      <link>https://cfsilva.com/posts/motivation_from_life_systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cfsilva.com/posts/motivation_from_life_systems/</guid>
      <description>In the common understanding, motivation often appears elusive, striking us randomly or evading us altogether. Some believe it&amp;rsquo;s discipline, not motivation, that propels us forward.&#xA;I propose it&amp;rsquo;s a harmonious blend of both.&#xA;Here&amp;rsquo;s how 10 Push-Ups a Day can transform your life: Motivation is not just a mental state; it&amp;rsquo;s woven into our life systems. It thrives as we cultivate daily habits, no matter how small, which accumulate momentum and transform our lives, like a snowball.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
